[A Dream Within A Dream]
[Episode 39]
[9:00]
[Huaipu Hall]
[8 hours ago, at about 9 a.m.]
Song Yimeng.
Song Yimeng!
Nan Heng!
Nan Heng,
send some people
to protect the Song family.
Do it now,
or Yiting and my father
will get in trouble.
Trouble?
What trouble?
I know you must find it
puzzling.
In a while,
you'll see Shangguan He
dressed in teal and enter the room.
He'll pull one foot back at the doorsill
and tell you
an off-the-books Qianyu troop
has been secretly planted
in Qianyu Mansion.
Fugui checked the plans
of garrison defenses
and saw
no records of Qianyu Army
being deployed last night.
Shanhu asked his friends
in relevant fields
and found that those people
were soldiers transferred from the borders
to the capital by Chu Guihong in secret.
I-I...
I don't understand what you're saying.
Chief...
Look!
Aren't we going to discuss
something important about Lord Qianyu?
Don't you think it's a bit too early
for intimate contact?
Am I right?
Come here.
Last night,
what did you find in Qianyu Mansion?
You truly guessed it right.
An off-the-books Qianyu troop
has been secretly planted
in Qianyu Mansion.
Fugui checked the plans
of garrison defenses
-and saw no records of Qianyu Army...
-See?
Shanhu asked his friends
in relevant fields,
and found that those people
were soldiers transferred from the borders
to the capital by Chu Guihong in secret.
Nan Heng,
look.
I'm right, aren't I?
That's because I've experienced
all of today's events twice.
It's true.
Trust me.
Then...
What will happen next?
Next,
the Emperor will be poisoned.
The Song family will be held hostage.
So,
we need to split up into two teams now
and stop those from happening.
Wait.
Why are you nodding?
She just woke up from sleep.
Are her words even believable?
I trust her.
[Qianyu Mansion]
[Kidnap Song Yiting
and her mother as a threat]
[Song Yimeng cooperates]
[Nan Heng shoots Song Yimeng
at the city tower]
You must listen to me this time.
Just stick to the plan.
All the events today are designed
for the hostage situation
on the city tower.
Only after the iconic scenes
happen as scheduled,
can I go back to the modern times
and write a perfect ending for you.
Where is this moth from?
Moth...
What's wrong?
The window...
That butterfly...
And your words...
All of this seems to have happened before.
What do you mean?
I'm right.
It all feels familiar.
I have a question.
Would things repeatedly happen
in this script world?
Or,
does reincarnation exist?
Reincarnation?
You mean "unlimited flow", right?
It does exist.
Song Yimeng experienced it
when she first entered
the script world.
At that time,
she kept getting married.
Things started all over after she died.
In our words, it is called
"stuck with a bug."
Things started again after she died?
Back then,
didn't she consistently
try to avoid Nan Heng
and marry you?
But the story disallowed it,
so she died and was reborn
many times.
Dead.
Reborn.
Then she experienced
the same events
at that given point in time repeatedly?
Yes.
Why do you ask?
When she is reborn,
will she have the memories
of her past lives?
Memories?
That is to say,
she can foresee the future.
Can she?
If that's the case,
she must know all of our plans now,
doesn't she?
Under these circumstances,
I'll have to preempt their attempts
and strike first.
[11:00]
[Imperial Study]
Let me peel it.
Okay.
Father, you eat it first.
Father...
Look how clumsy you are.
Let me peel it.
Wait,
Father.
Did you peel a tangerine for me before?
I'm the Emperor.
When have I ever peeled
tangerines for anyone?
This is the first time.
No.
I...
I find the setting here
very familiar. Why?
When the juice got on you,
I felt
it had happened before.
You're making nonsense again.
I...
Your Majesty!
Your Highness!
General!
Guihong?
Is there a problem with my eyes?
What are you doing?
Your Majesty,
this carries fatal toxins.
What kind of nonsense is that?
Rui bought this red tangerine for me.
How is it poisonous?
Guihong,
I...
Father,
I didn't put poison in it.
I'd never ever have the nerve
to do
an utterly unconscionable thing like that!
Have I determined this is your doing yet?
Chu Guihong,
how did you find out about this?
I just received a report.
The red tangerine vendor was seen
to put poison in his fruit
and then sell some
to the Eighteenth Prince.
I think
someone is plotting
against Your Majesty
and the Eighteenth Prince.
What?
Who
would do this to us?
The late Empress's death anniversary
is approaching.
Red tangerines...
The late Empress's death anniversary
is approaching.
Red tangerines were
Her Majesty's favorite.
were Her Majesty's favorite.
At this time every year,
the Eighteenth Prince
and Your Majesty would eat
red tangerines together
in memory of the late Empress.
How come I feel Heng has said it here too?
Not many people in the palace
know about this.
My guess is
that the plotter
must be
very close to Your Majesty
and the Eighteenth Prince.
Chu Guihong,
what are you implying?
How dare you!
You're hurling
a baseless accusation at the crown prince!
Yeah.
Guihong,
Heng is the crown prince now.
He has no reason to poison Father...
So what?
He has diabolical ambitions.
Out of fear of being replaced
if His Majesty changes his mind,
the crown prince might take a precaution.
Your Majesty,
this could be a rebellion.
To avoid further turmoil,
Your Majesty had better stay
in the bed chamber.
I'll bring Qianyu Army
into the palace to safeguard Your Majesty.
Chu Guihong,
are you trying to confine me here?
Protecting the sovereign
is my duty as an officer.
[Huanning Hall]
We're late.
The Emperor has ordered
to relieve the Imperial Guards.
Have this place guarded now.
Without my permission,
no one can be admitted to the chamber.
If there are violators,
kill them.
Got it.
Remember,
do whatever it takes to make him write
an imperial edict to eradicate Nan Heng.
Rest assured, General.
I'll get the imperial edict.
Last time,
he took action ahead of time.
Why is he doing it again now?
Qianyu Army
has quickly taken control of the palace.
Is the Emperor...
We must find out a way
to rescue the Emperor.
H-Heng...
Heng!
I...
Why are you here?
When Father attracted their attention,
I snuck out of the hall
through a hole for dogs.
That's the whole story.
He must've gone crazy!
He boldly confined the Emperor?
This is bad.
We must rescue Father now.
Heng,
listen,
before I escaped,
Father reminded me
to warn you
not to act rashly.
He will
try stalling for time.
Father also said,
my cousin...
Chu Guihong
is eager to get
an imperial edict to attack you.
Going out there now
is handing yourself over, isn't it?
He's right.
The first time the Emperor got in danger,
many people in the palace witnessed
Nan Rui
feeding him poisonous tangerines.
But things are different this time.
A street vendor's testimony alone
can hardly convince everyone.
What?
It...
When did I ever poison my father?
It was done by Chu Guihong.
He just framed you.
Chu Guihong put poison in the tangerines?
That's impossible.
H-H-He...
How could he have done it?
It was he who stopped Father
from eating the tangerines.
Right.
What made Chu Guihong
change his plan this time?
He has
either predicted our action,
or...
Is he also part of the unlimited flow now?
Does he have any memories
of the last two occasions?
Definitely not.
Then he must have
got some information in advance,
which changed his mind.
But his ultimate goal remains.
What "unlimited flow"?
It is to kill you in person.
Wait.
Why is this all so befuddling?
What do you mean
by "unlimited flow"?
What... I...
I know each word,
but I'm puzzled
when they combine.
We'll explain it to you later.
Now, I'll ask Fugui to send
you and my mother
to the Waning River Crescent.
Okay.
We lost on the previous two occasions
due to the lack of military strength.
This time,
I'm going to meet someone first.
[Righteousness]
Stop!
You've secretly transferred
Qianyu Army to the capital.
Why do you still need the command token?
As I told you,
I must change my fate.
What don't you understand?
After finishing all the iconic scenes,
I'll write a new ending
to your satisfaction!
No need to go the extra length, Father.
If I become the next emperor,
you'll be the Imperial Father.
The cold palace
where Nan Heng used to be confined
must be familiar to you.
Would you like to
spend the rest of your life there?
Chu Guihong!
You promised to let me
go back to the modern times!
-You...
-If you do go back,
my fate will fall in the palm
of your hand again, won it?
You...
From now on,
only I can decide my fate.
If you don't want
to live in the cold palace--
in the script, Nan Heng turns Song Yimeng
into a mutilated living corpse,
doesn't he?
How do you like it if you end up
that way?
Stay!
Guards!
I need help!
Help me!
Hurry.
Take Chu...
I am Lord Qianyu.
What are you doing?
Take him away.
Chu Guihong,
you crazy man!
I curse you!
When I go back,
I'll make you die in the script
a thousand times!
Too bad
that you can never go back.
I'm Lord Qianyu.
How dare you defy me?
Move!
Let go of me!
Keep moving!
I'm Lord Qianyu!
You...
Nan Heng!
Don't yell.
Nan Heng,
Chu Guihong has gone crazy.
He placed 5,000 soldiers outside the city.
Precisely at nine tonight,
they'll besiege you.
If you don't want to die,
quickly finish the iconic scenes
with Song Yimeng.
When I'm back to...
Still thinking about the iconic scenes?
Do you know you've already died twice?
I've died twice?
When?
According to Song Yimeng,
First,
Rong Hua killed you.
Then,
Chu Guihong killed you.
It was I who collected your body.
That reincarnation thing is true.
I'm telling you,
a new round of reincarnation has begun.
If you want to survive,
collaborate with me
to fight Chu Guihong.
Fight Chu Guihong?
Are you out of your mind?
I'm just a screenwriter.
I know how to type,
but not how to fight.
You looked down on us
fictional characters, didn't you?
I...
Weren't you omnipotent?
How about this?
You're here already.
Might as well make this visit count,
right?
Help me out of here.
I'll hide somewhere.
Then, you guys can
proceed to political struggles
or fights.
I won't hold you back, okay?
Hide somewhere?
This is a critical time.
Are you even a man?
Don't be so mean.
I'm just pointing out my incompetence,
aren't I?
I'm a tiny screenwriter,
not the male lead.
These glorious moments
of fighting and killing
should be reserved for you.
Nan Heng.
Heng...
My dearest Heng,
I've already had a hard time
in reality because of you.
I-In the script world,
please spare me from trouble.
Cut the crap.
I...
No matter who you are,
you can only be Lord Qianyu today.
Lord Qianyu?
Have some water.
Thank you.
Nan Heng,
how are you holding up?
If you really can't manage...
Don't worry.
I...
I'm coping well.
Don’t tell me you can die
and let reincarnation happen again
if the worst happens.
Listen,
this time,
I won’t let you get hurt.
But Chu Guihong commands
5,000 soldiers now.
Lord Qianyu hasn't agreed to help us yet.
What do you have
to fight Chu Guihong with?
Don't tell me you can count on
your plot armor as the male lead.
As you said, I'm the male lead.
The male lead has to
come up with
certain solutions
that only he can think of.
What's your plan?
My uncle told me before his execution
that he had 3,000 private soldiers
outside the city.
I have 3,000 private soldiers
stationing outside the city in secret.
Once Your Highness gives an order,
they'll raid the capital
from inside and outside.
The capital prefecture's office
has failed attempt to find this troop.
Therefore,
I asked Yao Qian
to lead the Nightwalkers
to look for clues.
They'll search every corner
on the outskirts
till these soldiers are found.
But it was you who revealed
Chancellor Gao's crimes.
Will his private soldiers
follow your commands?
I had Yao Qian take
a crown prince's edict with him.
These soldiers can choose to hide
and conceal their identities forever,
or to make amends by following me
to quell the unrest.
I believe most of them
will go for the latter.
The more people join us,
the higher the odds of us winning.
More people?
Perhaps
before your uncle's private soldiers
enter the capital,
we can recruit some people
and have them stall Chu Guihong for us.
What people?
Officials.
People from the martial arts world.
Residents in the capital.
They can all be our aides.
I-I'm having a stomachache.
Jia Ruru,
please hear me out.
Y-You...
Mrs. Li,
why wouldn't he help us?
Yunlong and I
even offered him a luminous pearl.
This big.
To fear is human.
The idea of fighting Chu Guihong
who holds a large army,
scares them even more.
I wish there were helpers from thin air.
Mrs. Li!
Mrs. Li.
Mrs. Shangguan
and Mr. Song are here.
Dad!
Yimeng,
what's the emergency?
Why did you tell us to come?
Let's talk over there.
Come on.
The Eighteenth Prince is here as well?
Nan Heng needs to
explain something to him.
I just hope he won't faint
upon hearing Heng's words.
Faint?
What exactly is going on?
Jixiang,
they must've reached the part
about the script world.
When I first heard it,
I reacted the same way.
Now, they must be
talking about the reincarnation.
This beautiful world
is filled with wonders.
Ignorant people are easily shocked.
The Eighteenth Prince and you
seldom travel far.
It's understandable for people
with scanty information like you
not to know these bizarre things.
Hope you don't feel inferior.
[Jixiang]
I've said too much.
You need time to process it.
Though Chu Guihong
has set you up three times,
his real target has always been me.
If
you can't bring yourself to fight him,
-I will...
-Heng.
Look,
you died so many times.
You must've been in a lot of pain.
This is all my fault.
When I first bought
those red tangerines,
if I had discovered the poison in them...
No.
I shouldn't have bought
those red tangerines at all.
Wait.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
I do.
Thoroughly and completely.
You're saying
that the Nightwalkers and you
will lure Chu Guihong's rebel forces
to the South City
to create a chance for me
to lead 300 Xuanjia soldiers
to charge into the palace
to rescue Father.
But, Heng,
we only have a small number of soldiers.
You've been defeated by Chu Guihong twice.
What if
you die again?
But we've gone this far now.
I...
I have an idea.
See if you find it feasible.
I'll lead Xuanjia Army to lie in ambush
in the South City in advance,
while you lure Chu Guihong
to go there alone.
Once he falls into our trap,
I'll suddenly appear from nowhere.
He'll be thrown into utter panic
and erupt into fury.
We'll be able to change our fate
when that happens.
Isn't it a good idea?
Not at all.
Heng,
you can count on me, your brother!
Stop with that gibberish.
Just do as I say.
I'll head to the South City.
You'll storm the palace.
But...
Without you...
If I do it alone, I'm afraid...
Those 300 Xuanjia soldiers
will be with you, right?
Plus, that great fighter
Jixiang will await you in the palace.
I'm sure you can rescue Father.
Don't worry.
Nan Rui,
you are my brother.
You can definitely do
what I can,
or even perform better than me.
Besides, don't forget
that you are heaven's chosen one
and Great Jing's symbol
of good fortune.
Okay.
I'll protect the palace.
You'll protect the capital.
The two of us
will definitely survive this time.
What did you say?
Chu Guihong is going to start a coup?
In less than six hours,
Qianyu rebels
will enter the capital.
How is that possible?
Lord Qianyu is reputed for his loyalty.
Why would he allow his son
to rise in rebellion?
Dad,
I don't have time
to explain everything to you.
But we must
stop Chu Guihong now.
Otherwise, Nan Heng, his people
and the entire Song family
will be in danger.
My goodness.
What can we do?
Alright.
Say no more.
It's just that this matter...
I...
Dad,
if Great Jing is in jeopardy,
will you brave all dangers
to protect the country?
This is my obligation.
I'll resolutely fulfill my duty.
That's enough.
Yiting,
what about you?
Will you do it too?
No need to give me lectures on morals.
I will go
wherever you go.
Madam,
what about you?
M-Me?
I...
I'm gutless and afraid of death.
I'm weak and...
You show great strength
when you hit me.
Can...
can that be the same thing?
Cut it out.
Tsk.
What about you guys?
It's okay.
If you are afraid,
you may leave now.
I won't force you to stay.
Let's go!
They...
They really left?
There are only the four of us now.
Nonetheless,
every new helper
represents new hope.
Right?
Your Highness!
Your Highness, we'll all go with you.
I'll make those who dare to hurt
the Song family pay a price!
This
can't move fast.
I'll go get some more rods.
Where did you get all these?
They were lying around
in the Waning River Crescent's Hall.
Put them down now.
I'm not planning to send you
onto the battlefield.
Yimeng,
what are you planning for us then?
I'm taking you lot to the South City
to join the Nightwalkers
in stallling Chu Guihong,
so he can't unite
with Qianyu reinforcements in time.
[Clear Waters and Serene Woods]
Your Highness,
you gave me a drink
before a battle starts.
It means you're discarding me.
How could Your Highness be so cruel to me?
How am I discarding you?
I'm simply letting you
accompany Rui to the palace.
Your Highness,
whenever you're up
for an important mission,
you'd always discard me
and bring Chu He along instead.
Your Highness,
Lord Qianyu is his godfather.
Chu He might harm you!
Let me ask you.
Who is the Emperor to me?
Your father.
What about Rui?
Your brother.
I'm assigning you to protect
my father and brother.
Yet you think of it as a trivial matter?
Your Highness, do you mean
I'm more important than Chu He?
It's unnecessary
to compare yourself with others.
Over all these years,
we've braved many deadly dangers together.
In my heart,
you're already my family.
Do you understand?
Rest assured, Your Highness.
I will complete this important task
Your Highness gave me.
Your Highness,
I'm heading to protect
your father-in-law and brother-in-law.
Guys,
[Big Fortune]
I'm not bragging here.
When I was only 15 years old,
I met a gang of bandits in the woods
on the outskirts of the capital.
Guess what?
I stood up to them...
I beat down ten of them on my own
and didn't get hurt at all.
How impressive.
You think that's a remarkable achievement?
Shanhu,
when I was being chased after
by officers and soldiers
in Jiangnan Province,
I defeated 100 enemies and safely escaped.
100?
100!
That's amazing.
Yunlong,
how many people can you fight at a time?
One.
Yunlong, you're seldom this humble.
I only have one target now-- Chu Guihong.
He's considered
as Great Jing's God of War.
Just leave him to Chief.
We should
stay out of it.
Shangguan He,
[Big Fortune]
are you slacking off again?
Mrs. Shangguan,
I'm going out to dig for information.
You guys talk.
Have you done the preparation
for the ambush against Qianyu Army?
Hurry up.
Go get it done!
[Big Fortune]
Don't stick around here.
Hurry!
Move!
Come on.
What's in it?
Wedding apparel.
Wedding apparel?
For whom?
We're getting married?
Right now?
Right here?
Shouldn't our wedding include
proper rituals
and our friends and family?
I don't care for
rituals
and audience.
Our marriage
is only about you and me.
Since you truly want to marry me,
we might as well get married today.
Yiting,
if I can come back alive,
the first thing I'll do is marry you.
Yimeng told me
that men who make promises of that kind
would usually end up
tragically.
The tombs of some of them
are even nowhere to find.
Shangguan He,
Today,
I will
either become your wife,
or...
cut your hair off
and tie it with mine.
As our hair strands entwine,
nothing can part this love divine.
Let the sky and earth be our witnesses.
We vow to the sun and moon
before this red knot
that we will be partners for life.
Song Yiting,
do you take me, Shangguan He,
to be your husband?
From now on...
No.
You don't want to get married now?
I mean,
that is not a good enough vow.
Isn't that a common wedding vow?
Let me take care of it.
Shangguan He,
do you take me
to be your lifelong partner?
From now on,
for richer
or for poorer,
in health
and in sickness,
will you comfort me,
love me,
protect me,
respect me
and stay with me
till death
do us part?
Yes, I do.
I do too.
You've taken the initiative many times.
Now, it's my turn.
♪ If frost etched traces of weariness ♪
♪ If surging clouds hid the stars ♪
♪ The gaze you once cast upon me ♪
♪ Does it still remember love and hate? ♪
♪ If the rising wind scatters the dust ♪
♪ If every dream must be awakened ♪
♪ How much of the past can we recognize? ♪
♪ In a single thought lies tenderness ♪
♪ Look at the vast heavens,
letting rain fall, indifferent to all ♪
In just a while,
a bitter war will begin.
♪ Watch how time quietly
waits for stories to take root ♪
But I haven't found a sufficient number
of helpers.
Don't worry.
I got a message from Yao Qian,
♪ Look at the way you're going,
destiny has it all planned out ♪
saying that he already found
the hideout
of my uncle's private soldiers.
Really?
Are they willing to help us?
♪ We lead remarkable lives
in this mundane world ♪
About 2,000 soldiers
would like to join us.
What's more, they can reach
the South City before midnight.
That's great.
As long as
we stall Chu Guihong for two more hours,
we will meet our reinforcements
and change our fate against all odds.
♪ Look at the sky, flowers bloom
and fragrance fills the air ♪
♪ The sound of heartbeats
resonates in the passing time ♪
♪ Look at the way you're going,
destiny has it all planned out ♪
♪ We lead remarkable lives
in this mundane world ♪
What's up?
Why are you smiling?
I suddenly recalled
something said by the screenwriter.
He said, in this script world,
each person...
is just
an insignificant fictional character.
But it doesn't seem to be true now.
Look.
Tonight,
each and every
Xuanjia soldier
and Nightwalker
will be writers of this script world.
That's right.
Tonight,
there won't be such thing as
supporting roles or fictional characters.
Everybody will play the lead.
Then, as the female lead,
I must channel all my energy to the show.
[Relay & Receive]
The old Song Yimeng
would love to lay back and slack off,
hoping that one day,
a great hero
would show up
with colorful clouds under his feet
and make all the problems go away.
But now, I've come to realize one thing.
Indeed,
in everyone's life,
there are heroes.
But the biggest one of them
is definitely
the uncompromising
and unyielding his or her own self.
Tonight, let us join hands
to fight as hard as we can
and leave no regrets.
Fight as hard as we can.
Leave no regrets.
Let's go!
Yes!
♪ I ride on the wind
of the waning river crescent ♪
♪ Hate the injustice in the world ♪
♪ Loyalty and righteousness
weigh on both sides of the scale ♪
♪ Wield the knife
to carve a rift in the hell ♪
Qianyu rebels
are endangering Great Jing.
Traitors are running rampant
♪ The waning river crescent sheds light
over the old chess board ♪
and persecuting the loyal.
♪ On the 32 sandalwood tables ♪
♪ The gamblers toss their bucks ♪
All the people
♪ Beneath the dice cup
hide secret letters ♪
shall raise the flag of justice
♪ The storyteller unfolds the story ♪
to protect the sovereign
♪ The code is in the 13th line ♪
and the country!
♪ I dip cold tea to write spy info ♪
♪ The ink seeps into the board ♪
Protect Great Jing!
♪ Half a wall falls
in the golden celestial palace ♪
Protect Great Jing!
♪ The storyteller closes his fan
and shakes the dice cup ♪
At nine tonight,
♪ As the moon sinks to the west,
dawn light shines on the corridor ♪
The main forces of the Nightwalkers and I
will lure Chu Guihong
to Anhe Pier in the South City.
♪ We've all hidden in the market
and released chimney smoke ♪
Large troops can't pass through
the narrow streets in the South City.
♪ The pawnshop owner weeps,
counting silver notes ♪
So, Qianyu Army will have to
split up and take three routes,
♪ The pledged military order
is now riddled with decay ♪
if they are to unite with Chu Guihong.
♪ A wine banner
pierces the midnight haze ♪
Shangguan He, Yunlong, Shanhu and you
are responsible for ambushing
♪ A secret stronghold
lies dormant on the canal map ♪
Chu Guihong's reinforcements.
Rest assured.
♪ I ride on the wind
of the waning river crescent ♪
Our people have lain in ambush
on these three routes.
♪ Hate the injustice in the world ♪
♪ Loyalty and righteousness
weigh on both sides of the scale ♪
♪ Wield the knife
to carve a rift in the hell ♪
Then,
Fugui will lead 300 Xuanjia soldiers
to accompany Rui
to rescue the Emperor in the palace.
God of Earth,
Bodhisattva,
Dragon King,
Kitchen God,
and...
God of Wealth,
Lord Guan,
today,
I'm leading a troop
to defend the royal palace.
I am heaven's chosen one,
the symbol of good fortune.
You will
look out for me, won't you?
Please bless me,
my father
and Heng
to return safely,
to triumph over adversity
and to bring victory home.
I promise I'll place you in a proper room
and present offerings to you.
I'll worship you
with the same food I eat.
Okay?
Please.
Your Highness,
it's time to set out.
Coming right up.
No need to cover them up.
♪ The waning river crescent sheds light
over the old chess board ♪
I saw everything.
♪ On the 32 sandalwood tables ♪
Compared with those irrelevant divinities,
♪ The gamblers toss their bucks ♪
maybe I'm more of help.
♪ Beneath the dice cup
hide secret letters ♪
Don't talk nonsense!
♪ The storyteller unfolds the story ♪
Get a move on.
♪ The code is in the 13th line ♪
Fugui!
♪ I dip cold tea to write spy info ♪
Wait up!
♪ The ink seeps into the board ♪
Fugui!
Oh.
Good heavens!
Why not help me?
Carry these for me, will you?
Fugui!
Junior General,
the Qianyu soldiers
outside the city have assembled.
Once you give an order,
they'll hurry to the South City
to unite with us.
Everyone,
set out for the South City
to eliminate all rebels!
Set out for the South City
Release!
Let's go!
[Govern with Morals]
Your Majesty,
I'll give you one last chance.
Write an imperial edict
to eradicate Nan Heng the rebel now.
Otherwise, after nine o'clock tonight,
you won't be able to hold a pen anymore.
[Huanning Hall]
Mr. Song,
are you nervous?
I used to be the mighty Minister of War.
I'm not nervous.
Are you really not?
I really am not.
Blow.
Ignite.
Throw.
Hide.
Right?
Right.